https://www.treadstoneperformance.com/privacy-policy

order now
Items in cart: Subtotal:
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE
Treadstone Performance Engineering Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. When you shop on our website, we collect personal information from you such as name, address, email, phone number and/or credit card information. This information is used for billing purposes for filling customer's orders, contacting customers to inform them of order status and sending promotional information. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Treadstone Performance Engineering Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on our website.
LOG FILES
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement within the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
SHARING
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any person individually.
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to charge users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
SECURITY
Treadstone Performance Engineering Inc. takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.
When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as name, address, phone number, credit card information), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry, SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. When you submit your order, the sensitive information is sent to our secure server that is retrieved only by authorized administrators via secure connection and pass worded logs.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (i.e. for billing purposes or service representatives) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected.
join our email list
You’ll be first to know about Treadstone Performance Engineering new products, discounts and special events!
Email address
You have successfully signed up to get the best deals.
You have already signed up to get the best deals!!!
SUBMIT
Shop by Vehicle
Select Make
ACURAALFA ROMEOASTON MARTINAUDIBENTLEYBMWBUICKCADILLACCHEVROLETCHRYSLERDAEWOODODGEFERRARIFIATFORDGENESISGMCHONDAHUMMERHYUNDAIINFINITIISUZUJAGUARJEEPKIALAMBORGHINILAND ROVERLEXUSLINCOLNLOTUSMASERATIMAZDAMERCEDESMERCURYMINIMITSUBISHINISSANOLDSMOBILEPLYMOUTHPONTIACPORSCHERAMSAABSALEENSATURNSCIONSMARTSRTSUBARUSUZUKITESLATest MakeTOYOTAVOLKSWAGENVOLVO
Select Model
Select Year
Select Type
Tires
Wheels
Accessories
SEARCH
Select Width
36789101112131415161718192021222324252627282930313233343536373839404210511011512012513514515015516016516617017518018519019520521522523524525025526527528529530030530931031532533534535537538540040542544570043,296
Select Ratio
04.5056.50788.5099.501010.501111.501212.2012.501313.501414.5015.501616.5017.501818.5019.502021.50222325303435404546505155606570717580859095700
Select Diameter
128910111213141515.3015.501616.501717.50181919.5020212222.50232424.5025262830313246155480
Add a Different Rear Tire SizeDifferent Size
SEARCH NOW
Select Width
36789101112131415161718192021222324252627282930313233343536373839404210511011512012513514515015516016516617017518018519019520521522523524525025526527528529530030530931031532533534535537538540040542544570043,296
Select Ratio
04.5056.50788.5099.501010.501111.501212.2012.501313.501414.5015.501616.5017.501818.5019.502021.50222325303435404546505155606570717580859095700
Select Diameter
128910111213141515.3015.501616.501717.50181919.5020212222.50232424.5025262830313246155480
Select Width
36789101112131415161718192021222324252627282930313233343536373839404210511011512012513514515015516016516617017518018519019520521522523524525025526527528529530030530931031532533534535537538540040542544570043,296
Select Ratio
04.5056.50788.5099.501010.501111.501212.2012.501313.501414.5015.501616.5017.501818.5019.502021.50222325303435404546505155606570717580859095700
Select Diameter
128910111213141515.3015.501616.501717.50181919.5020212222.50232424.5025262830313246155480
Add Same Rear & Front Tire SizeSame Size
SEARCH NOW
×
Search by Vehicle
Select Make
ACURAALFA ROMEOASTON MARTINAUDIBENTLEYBMWBUICKCADILLACCHEVROLETCHRYSLERDAEWOODODGEFERRARIFIATFORDGENESISGMCHONDAHUMMERHYUNDAIINFINITIISUZUJAGUARJEEPKIALAMBORGHINILAND ROVERLEXUSLINCOLNLOTUSMASERATIMAZDAMERCEDESMERCURYMINIMITSUBISHINISSANOLDSMOBILEPLYMOUTHPONTIACPORSCHERAMSAABSALEENSATURNSCIONSMARTSRTSUBARUSUZUKITESLATest MakeTOYOTAVOLKSWAGENVOLVO
Select Model
Select Year
Select Sub Model 1
Select Sub Model 2
Select Sub Model 3
SEARCH
